♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ next sunday, a.d. ♪
♪ There was a guy
named joel ♪
♪ not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ he worked
at gizmonic institute ♪
♪ just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ he did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ but his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ so they shot him
into space ♪
♪ we'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
- ♪ the worst we can find ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
- ♪ and we'll monitor his mind ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ now keep in mind
joel can't control ♪
- ♪ where the movies
begin or end ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ to make his robot friends ♪
Let's go.
- Cambot.
- Pan left.
Hi, girl.
What a cool guy.
A wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
- ♪ and other science facts ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ then repeat to yourself
"it's just a show ♪
♪ "I should really
just relax ♪
♪ for... ♪
Did-- did I show
you guys my magical,
whimsical
squirting flower?
Yes! About
a gazillion times.
Oh. Well,
did I show you my rash?
[All shout, groan]
Don't do it, please!
Hi everybody, welcome
to the satellite of love.
My name's joel robinson.
About three weeks ago,
I set up this
holo-clown sequence.
It would cheer up the bots,
but now I can't
get it to turn off,
and it's getting hard
to sleep at night,
and I'm tasting metal.
Hey, little girl. Would you
like a salted nut roll?
Aah! Joel, joel--
[clown screams]
Why are you yelling?
Shut up! Shut up!
You think I like it,
being stuck in limbo with you?
No! Get on your
orange and yellow knees
and kiss my clown feet
that I haven't killed you.
Joel, this is getting weird.
You gotta do something.
I'm working on it.
[Magic voice]
Joel, do something.
I hate those clowns,
and I don't even exist.
That's the one.
Joel robinson!
Don't you do that!
- Don't you do that!
- I have to do it!
[All scream over each other]
- Commercial sign now.
- Well. Let's not
- do that again.
- Oh boy.
We'll be right back.
[Servo as beat poet]
Clowns are raining down.
Hear the scream
of the grease paint.
Danger. Clown puddles.
Nice haiku, tom. Very good.
Crow, you're next.
Oh, the captain
and tennille are calling.
Ah. Robinson. Servo.
Mr. T. Robot.
Our invention this week
is inspired by
today's experiment,
attack of
the giant leeches.
In ye olden times,
alchemists believed that leeches
served medicinal purposes.
- So do we.
- Yes,
and we've found that
the common freshwater leech
can serve the same purpose
as a nicotine patch.
And being neither
food nor drug,
there's no pesky
fda regulation
to impede your progress.
And I can
experiment at will.
- Frank?
- At your service.
Our subject, frank,
has been trying to quit smoking
for quite some time.
He's a three-pack-a-day man.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are. Shut up.
- [Frank mouths words]
- Now, this leech--
- we'll call him patches.
- Aah!
Uh, when applied
to the neck and head area,
- will suck
any desire to smoke--
- no, no, no.
- Out of frank.
- No! No! No! No!
I'm the sum of my vices!
I have my pain, my happiness,
my losses, my love!
My struggles!
My hobbies! Mylanta!
I want to live!
I want to live and love
and learn and live!
But this won't hurt a bit.
Okay.
There you go.
Now, patches,
I'm depending on you,
you slug.
Hey, this is the most
action I've gotten--
frank. Back to you, joel.
Well, sirs, as you know,
puberty is that time
when childhood
crosses that
mighty threshold
- to adulthood.
- Mm-hmm.
Kids can't wait
for it to start.
And grown-ups can't wait
for it to leave.
- [Bots chuckle]
- It's springtime for your body,
and you're about to bloom
into beautiful flora.
But as you know,
being an adolescent
is time-consuming.
And that's why
we came up with this.
The satellite of love
insty adolescent kit.
Yeah. Why waste your teendom
in tortuous flux
when those
funny feelings downstairs
can be taken care of
in a jiffy?
Get ready.
You'll have to start
showering daily
- as sebaceous bile--
- oh, no, no, no!
Included in the kit
does double-duty
on your scalp,
face, and underarms.
Ew, and my back too.
Yeah, and don't forget
the octaves you'll encompass
when you finally encounter
our minty-fresh
hormonal spray.
[Voice cracking]
Hello, suzie. Wanna go
to the snow days dance
with me?
And that's when your face
turns beet-red.
But it's okay,
'cause suzie won't notice.
Because you'll be
covered with pimples.
You guys just
don't understand me!
That's right.
Now that you're a teen,
the most innocent remarks
by friends and family
will be construed
as personal attacks.
Oh, and what's that
supposed to mean?
Well, fortunately,
each kit comes
with its own
personal retort cards.
With comebacks like,
"you just have no clue!"
"Who was in my room?"
And "you guys are
so phony!"
You're not the boss of me!
Hey, but there's more.
- [Servo mutters]
- Food pills.
Yes, you'll span
the emotional globe
when you experience
everything from
mild nausea
and persistent dread
to ecstatic feelings
of immortality.
--Think I'm stupid
or something?
All this in one afternoon.
I don't care anymore.
Great, but I still
don't have my license.
Oh, listen, mister.
If you don't like it,
you can stay in a hotel
down the street.
- What do you think, sirs?
- Jerk.
Very amusing, joel.
But let's not forget
why you're up there.
To watch really bad movies.
And now,
a dr. Clayton forrester
presentation.
Attack of the giant
leeches.
Oh, you're doing homework,
all right.
- Oh yeah, you are--
- I don't care.
You guys are so lame--
- [alarm blares]
- Oh, we got movie sign!
I don't care!
I don't care! I don't care!
You're not my father,
you know.
Oh yeah?
♪ Behold...
King of the sea ♪
♪ for fabled atlantis's
prince of the deep ♪
Oh look, it's the undersea
football all-stars!
They played u.S.C. Today.
[All]
♪ hey ♪
♪ it's the undersea
kingdom ♪
♪ for you and for me ♪
♪ and it's fun ♪
[Servo hums 1812 overture]
Looks like rush hour
on spaghetti junction.
Ooh, it's all
whirly-twirly.
- Oh--
- huh?
Oh, it's ben-hur.
I've seen this before.
Oh.
Hey! Hey, you guys!
Do we know where we're--
oh, I thought so.
- Come on. Come on!
- Back this way.
They have no clue, do they?
G. Heileman brewing company,
la crosse, wisconsin.
When in las vegas,
visit excalibur.
Ooh.
[Servo hums with score]
Beneath the ocean floor,
it's all full of mildew
down there.
Let's go gather around
the water cooler.
- We are the water cooler.
- Oh.
I love that one.
Annapolis a day
keeps the doctoris away.
[Bots laugh]
[All]
♪ we're walkin'
really really fast♪
really really fast ♪
♪ and then we're walk... ♪
Congratulations, soldiers.
Go out and kill.
Oh. Here. One for you.
Congratulations.
Go out and kill.
Ooh-- oh.
How about it, doc?
Do you think I'll live?
You look kind of
weak and puny,
- but I think
you'll pull through.
- I'm kidding, of course!
You're one of
the finest specimens
to ever come through here.
Thank you, sir.
Next.
Great chaps. I wish
we had more like him--
ah, keep your mind
on your work.
You're in enough trouble
as it is.
--Too bad
this is the last year.
He'll make a grand
naval officer.
He'll make several of them.
Hey, he's posing
for a wheaties box.
[All scream]
[Servo hums, raspberries]
I am the god of hellfire!
All these people are dead now.
Isn't that weird?
Think about it--
oh no, a football game
has broken out,
ladies and gentlemen!
I don't know
what to make of it!
This makes me lonesome for
my old electric
football game.
[Bots]
Aww.
It's good plumber man day
today.
What're those lab technicians
doing on the field?
The ball's back from center.
Goes to smith
and reverts to corrigan.
Corrigan--
oh look.
Gets the fullback,
knocks him down!
Looks like they're playing
in chocolate.
It's the hershey bowl.
--Are coming in!
He hits back, knocks him over!
[Servo mimics mud squelching]
[Servo raspberries]
--Crash corrigan,
captain of the navy team.
You know, in the future,
people will pay
- to see women do this.
- Ooh.
Take it back! My sister does not
swim towards tube ships!
Oh, smooth. Smooth--
[clears throat]
[All]
♪ well, I'd like
to know where ♪
♪ you got the notion ♪
♪ oh, I'd like
to know where ♪
♪ you got the notion ♪
♪ --like to know where
you got the notion ♪
Wait a minute, son.
What do you want?
I've gotta see
lieutenant corrigan right away.
You can't go in there.
It's against orders.
But I tell ya, I gotta see him.
It's important!
I'm his son. He doesn't
know about me yet.
Even if I let you in,
you couldn't
talk to the lieutenant now.
He's busy.
- Nice shoes.
- All right.
[Crow chuckles]
Little jerk.
Hmm.
Wow, jeepers, hot dog!
And everywhere, the smell of men
enjoying themselves.
Ooh. Ooh!
Uh-oh.
I'll show them.
I'm gonna jump off!
No! Don't do it!
And now back to
men with little pants.
[Bots grunt]
♪ Oh, she came in through
the bathroom window ♪
Uh-oh, he's having
an episode.
- Good work, jimmy!
- Jimmy smits.
- Don't let him pin ya, son--
- give him a wedgie!
- You almost had him that time--
- triple herman!
Whoo! Wet willy!
It was.
The tin drum.
- Ooh.
- Let's go down the slide
like this!
[Bots]
Whee!
Hold him!
You know, there's something
sick about this, joel.
Yeah. I call it
history, tom.
- Mm-hmm.
- Victory at sea.
Now you got him, crash!
Give him the airplane spin!
Good idea, kid.
Why didn't I think of that?
[Bots]
Huh?
- Benny!
- Don't be a hero!
- Hold tight!
- Don't need that.
- Hey.
- Hold it!
- Whoop!
[Monkey chirps, screams]
Ah, just save the kid.
Stop showing off.
Yeah, that's what happens
when you spend a lot of time
around sailors, you know.
Thank god they built this place
like a jungle gym.
Hold on, let me
close the window first.
Let's go, come on.
I got you.
- Hooray!
- Give us barabbas!
Eh, catch him, you mugs.
[Servo screams]
Aah, you got acne
all over your back-- yuck!
- [Crow monkey-chirps]
- Hey kid, feel free
to dig your heel
into my groin.
Now somebody's
gotta save me.
[Bots chuckle]
Thanks, friend.
- Hold tight, billy.
- Okay.
[Crow hums, strains]
Yay! Whoo!
- Ta-da!
- [All whistle]
I thought
the kid was a goner.
What were you
doing up there?
Dad sent me over to get you,
but they wouldn't let me in.
Has he had another
earthquake warning?
Yeah. He wants you
to come right over.
Well, wait until
I get into my clothes.
I'm going over to
professor norton's laboratory.
Put on a sarong.
That'll be all you need.
What you say is very
interesting, professor norton--
- but stupid.
- But I still can't believe
that this little machine
can predict earthquakes.
Not only predicts,
but prevents them.
- And it makes toast.
- If you get close enough
to the source.
- Hmm?
- Oh, there you are,
lieutenant.
The signals are
coming in much stronger.
Ooh, the earth
just moved for me.
This is ms. Compton,
staff writer of the times.
Well, everybody knows
crash corrigan.
Everybody digs bill evans. So?
Answer unclear. Ask again.
- Popcorn's ready.
- And it makes
three different kinds
of gelati.
--The signal, again.
They've been sending it
every five minutes.
"They?" just who
do you mean by "they?"
- Comedy central.
- Professor norton maintains
that these signals must be
the work of some human agency.
Apparently coming from
the bottom of the ocean.
Oh, the william morris
agency-- huh?
--Fantastic yarn about
the lost continent of atlantis.
Exactly. Only now I have
some definite evidence.
Let me get in my costume
and tell you about it.
Now, pretend
I'm a swarthy pirate.
- This is pure aurichalcum.
- No, I'm not.
A metal made by fusing
gold and copper.
- Gopper.
- The secret of this process
was lost for the atlanteans.
What does that prove?
Well, according
to every test,
the idol couldn't be more than
a couple of years old.
Something made recently.
I found it during a recent trip
I made in my rocket submarine
in this general location.
You have a rich inner life,
don't you?
--Where the ancient
continent of atlantis
was reported to have sunk
thousands of years ago.
Contrary to popular belief,
atlantis did not
sink overnight,
but during
a period of years.
That's great, gramps--
get the medication.
--Ample opportunity
to construct
a roof of aurichalcum
over the city
and keep out the ocean--
- aah! The film's melting.
- Oh-- ooh.
It's a better world.
Xanadu. Stately underwater home
of charles foster kane.
Cost? No fish can say.
It's a denver pyle statue.
I beg of you to take safety
in the citadel.
- Hey-- oh.
- Poseidon, god of atlantis,
has never forsaken his people
in time of need.
Jiffy pop's ready.
I promise you,
he will not do so now.
[Joel mimics trumpet]
Imperial.
--Until we have broken
the power of this evil usurper,
unga khan.
Oh no! The king's mad!
He's gonna
make us pretend
we're the rockettes again!
Run!
[Servo mimics trumpet]
It's the 1968
chrysler merrimac.
- Fondue.
- [All] Mmm.
Our men are outnumbered.
The city is about to fall.
You know, mayor dinkins
just ain't cuttin' it, is he?
[Servo hums]
Say.
♪ Me and my shadow ♪
♪ walking down the avenue ♪
Eh, must be a monday.
[Servo mimics trumpet]
Traffic lights must be out.
- Yep.
- [Servo mimics horse whinny]
Can you believe this crap?
Hey, look, dung beetles.
I don't want that!
[Servo mimics spring]
He was my favorite.
Ooh.
Ken just exploded, sir.
They bomb horses,
don't they?
[Servo mimics beeping]
Backing up.
There's the bomb
going into the air shaft.
Ooh.
This place looks like
a bomb just hit it.
[Bots groan]
[Servo mimics tiny engine]
Jane, I'm home!
David crosby, no!
I am pleased to report
that sharad's army
has been driven within
the walls of the sacred city.
Good. Recall the troops.
With those religious fanatics
under control,
I'll have no more interference
with my plans
to destroy the upper world.
[Crow chuckles]
You are really something, boss.
I think this is your year.
Your hat's very creative
today, kyle.
When you do succeed
in sending him
to the bottom of the sea,
atlantis will rise once more
to its former place in the sun,
and you will be
ruler of all things.
Start the disintegrator.
D'ah, okay.
[Servo hums with score]
Gotta finish a giant rolaid
first, sir.
[Crow groans]
Oh look, here's daniel
in the lion's den.
- Oh.
- This clown's making change.
This is a giant
welch's grape jelly machine,
and I'm outta here!
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
Good night now.
- Camera crew from real life.
- Ooh.
Set it for stun.
Let's play some metal! Whoo!
You clinking, clanking,
clattering collection
of caliginous junk!
Oh look, he's packing
a tummy-sizer.
♪ The night chicago died ♪
♪ na-na-na, na-na-na ♪
♪ chicago died ♪
♪ brother, what a night
the people saw ♪
--Communication cut off.
Red cross is appealing
for doctors.
Special teams are running
supplies to the stricken area.
- Hmm. You in there?
- Sold american.
Rushing the militia
to the scenes of the disaster.
But now on
the lighter side of the news.
Saint claire?
That's only
300 miles from here.
Yes, and according
to my calculations,
another severe shock
will occur any moment.
- Bang.
- --Put that
counteracting machine
- aboard the submarine
right away.
- D'ah, okay.
You mean you're going down
to try and stop this place?
What a story this will make
for my paper.
Troy tempest, phones,
equals stingray.
Gray lady down, for contel.
Professor norton. Norton!
Get in here.
Oh, you're getting in here.
I don't know.
We're on a level keel,
but we're being dragged down
by some mysterious force.
The plot?
We're out of
baking soda, sir.
This sub is powered
by fizzies.
[Crow as james mason]
I want to take us down
to 20,000 leagues.
Meanwhile,
in young billy's bathtub.
Yeah, billy bathtub.
What a terrible movie.
No no, no, crow.
Check it out,
there are fish out there!
See.
Hey, they got
♪ a genie automatic
garage door ♪
- ♪ picker-upper ♪
- that's a swiss-army joke.
Sorry.
They're in the tunnel.
Bring them up
to the atlantic sea.
Do you think
I'm losing weight, sir?
[Servo hums with score]
When in coral gables,
florida,
visit crash corrigan cove.
We're at the surface.
I can see land.
Captain billy.
Impossible! According
to the depth indicator,
we're still some
10,000 feet down.
You know, I think they give
that kid too much freedom.
That's land, all right.
We're moving into a small--
yep, that's land.
I've seen it before.
Yep, definitely.
Wait a minute.
I think we're on
the pirates
of the caribbean ride.
- Big sub.
- Gee, we're on the surface.
I knew colonel kurtz
was close.
He was real close.
He knows scotty.
[All guffaw]
[Servo raspberries]
--Out the imperial guards,
and kill the dorky guy!
I hate comic relief.
- [Siren beeps]
- Is that your beeper?
- Nope.
- That's not me,
I don't think.
Oh.
I command that
his supreme majesty
- unga khan--
- who's he looking at?
--A detachment
of the imperial guard
will proceed at once
to the inland sea
and capture the stranger
from the upper world.
Put your skirt down.
--My horse, quickly!
Number one patrol, now.
Number one patrol,
prepare to move out.
That's us, boys.
Come on! It's time
for the big
hawaiian number.
Hey! Come on, everybody!
Whoo.
Hey, it's the poderosa
under the sea.
You know what? I think
that's a matte painting.
- Check it-- you see?
- Yeah.
We now join fitzcarraldo,
already in progress.
[Men scream]
Ooh. They running over
somebody?
Yee-hah!
This looks like
a fine place to set down
my pasty white bottom.
Well, they're certainly
well-dressed for adventure.
- Mm-hmm.
- Here we are, 10,000 feet
- below sea level.
- And me without my rubbers.
--In another world.
Hey, he's being followed
by michael nesmith.
Hey, did you know
my mom invented liquid paper?
- [Parrot squawks]
- Tookie! Tookie!
You'd better
submerge the submarine
while we investigate
this place.
All right.
Hey, did you remember
to close the hatch?
- D'oh!
- Oh!
Well, remember where
we parked, everyone.
- We're in the giraffe lot.
- We have to hide
the control box.
- Up there's a good place.
- Yes, that'll do.
Do you think we'd better wait
for briney and salty?
Briney and salty?
The pretzel twins!
--Sinbad the parrot.
Hi, everybody.
Here's where those two roads
diverge into a yellow wood!
Take the one less traveled.
That is one sweet chariot.
SHIRLEY MacLAINE.
- No, we are lost, r2.
- [Crow and joel whistle]
Owie! Ow-ow-ow-ouch!...
Shouldn't they be riding
side-saddle in those skirts?
Some of them are.
- [Servo whistles]
- No, you go that way.
You'll be breaking down
in no time.
[Servo whistles]
Hey, it's the 34 horsemen
of the apocalypse.
Ow. Ow ow ow. Ow ow.
Ouch, that burns, ouch.
Hey, check it out. It says,
"bill shatner was here."
Great. They're letting
jay north lead the pack here.
[Servo chuckles]
- Look, dad.
- How come they all turned
when he said "dad?"
Unless my calculations
are wrong,
we've come across
the lost continent of atlantis.
I'd say your calculations
are wrong.
It must be a mirage.
No, the mirage
is on the strip.
Listen.
And around
the clubhouse turn,
it's apartment house
with plenty of room
with bird droppings on the rail
coming around the bend.
Uh, look, this is what starts
those chain accidents.
That's no illusion--
it's a world of illusion.
Look! Soldiers.
Wait there! We're coming
to attack you!
Just keep out of sight.
Let's find out if
they're friends or enemies.
If they kill me,
they're probably enemies.
Uh, taxi, I say--
- taxi!
- Hey!
After 'em!
Aah. He's a real diplomat.
[Servo hums]
Get him, girls.
He hit buddy!
[Servo grunts, strains]
Hey, get this. I can see up
trent's skirt from here.
Okay. Hand me up that horse.
Uh-oh.
I got a crazy idea,
but it just might work!
No way they're gonna
pants me and make me-- aah!
Whoo.
Well, I never
rid a horsey before.
He's escaped.
Send out the juggernaut!
'Nuff said. Live to serve.
[All hum]
Wait, we need that horse!
- Idiot.
- You sure fooled 'em
this time, crash.
Let's get back
to the submarine.
But the soldiers!
What about them?
I'll tell you later.
We've no time to lose!
- [All scream]
- Well, right about that time,
the boys did a little body work
on the old general lee.
Hot-blooded,
check it and-- huh?
[ALL HUM '60s BATMAN THEME]
Some sort of a war tank.
[All]
Oh, I can see-- a war tank?!
Excuse me, have you seen
any earthlings?
- Oh. Oh.
- Steady.
- Hold me.
Okay boys, de-louse them.
Ooh, right in the nostril.
[Joel whispers]
Fisher. Fisher.
- They're not human!
- Yeah, we noticed.
Stop. Wait. Come back.
[Crow mimics plane crash]
--That crevice.
♪ I'm a little teapot ♪
♪ short and stout ♪
♪ this is my handle ♪
♪ this is my gun ♪
♪ one is for pouring,
one is for fun ♪
[Servo chuckles]
Pretty good.
D'oh!
- Silly string!
- [Diana screams]
Gee, lady, scream
in someone else's ear.
- Really.
- Everybody down!
You two get
behind that rock.
Count off by ones, everyone!
[All]
One! One! One!
Here, billy.
You draw their fire.
- Diane!
- Ooh, the strangers have
- escaped the volkites--
- ah, I hate when they talk
during the movie.
Oh.
Hmm.
[Servo hums with score]
Fast!
The invisible ray gun
will soon stop them.
It's not very invisible.
I can see it.
All right, billy,
when I throw you off here,
flap your arms like crazy.
Launch the disintegrator!
G.e. We bring
good things to death.
You know, I liked meg ryan
in this role better.
Welp, this is it.
Looks like I'm gonna
be forced to
push you off, davis.
- --The mountain.
- Hit him in the mouth?
Oh no, they're shooting
hot dogs at him.
- [Crow laughs]
- No!
Hold the mustard
on that one.
Admiral,
deploy the cheddarwurst.
Oh no!
Ooh.
Oh wow.
Blindsided by another short.
- Are you guys okay?
- Oh, don't worry, joel.
I'm feeling
no unusual effects from it.
Isn't that right, billy?
[Crow affects voice]
That's right, crow.
That's really nice, crow.
That's...
You know, joel,
for the life of me,
I can't understand
the appeal of these old serials.
Well, that's no big mystery,
my little fireplug.
You see, they actually have
kind of a historic quality.
You know,
if it's in the 1930's,
and you're interested
in taking over the world,
you gotta get gussied up
to beat the band.
Hah. No kidding.
Just look at the elaborately
flamboyant costumes
the bad guys
were gadding about in.
Togas. Electric helmets.
Dance belts.
- Fascist underoos.
- Right. Right, exactly.
And I thought it'd be fun
as a thought experiment
for you guys to tell me
how you would dress up
if you were gonna
take over the world.
Hmm. Oh, you know,
I'd bronze my skin,
put on 40 pounds,
and dress like bea arthur.
- Smart.
- I'd wear
a lone ranger mask
and a swimsuit
made of string cheese.
Good idea,
very thoughtful.
Okay, uh...
Say you've got your costume.
What would your caper be?
I mean, what would you do
to take over the world?
Oh, I'd freeze
all the world's oceans.
But then I guess that means
I'd have to dress like
dick button.
Yeah. I'd send california
tumbling into the ocean.
The atlantic ocean.
After showering, talc,
and changing into
my frito bandito costume.
- I see. Well...
- Nice touch.
Once you've
taken over the world,
- what would you do then?
- Ooh!
I'd turn all those
who oppose me
into the boy
in the plastic bubble.
For obvious reasons.
I'd declare march
"liza month!"
[Bots]
Whoo!
Well, it's fun to dream,
you know.
But you can bet that
anybody seriously interested
in world domination
is gonna end up looking
like a real snickerdoodle.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I'll deal with you later.
Back to the drill, frank.
You will bow down
before me, son of jor-el.
Bow down.
[All, with score]
♪ of the giant leeches ♪
♪♪ [servo hums]
Looks like
an e.E. Cummings book cover.
Yeah.
♪♪ [Servo hums]
Type setting
by smith corona.
[Servo, with score]
♪ original story ♪
♪ and screenplay
by leo gordon ♪
♪ leo gordon leo gordon ♪
♪♪ [servo scats]
Ooh!
Neat, huh?
Well, I'll have
a dick rubin.
Hold the sauerkraut.
Ryder rents sound services.
♪♪ [Servo hums]
Laszlo, also bringing you
a fine line of cosmetics
for aging socialites
and social x-rays.
- Hey!
- Roger corman!
[All cheer]
- Huh?
- Wonder if they're related?
Oh, no.
Mm. A title sequence
named desire.
Stella!
Then folks started
paying for their groceries
with old cars.
Nothing you could
do about it.
Nope.
This looks the right side
of the wrong side of the tracks.
Mm-hmm.
[All]
Norm!
- [All laugh]
- Now wait a minute,
wait a minute.
The hee-haw writing session.
So I was thinking lulu could
pop up behind some corn!
Now that's funny!
- Liz!
- Is more!
Do you hear me, girl?
Tell little jerry lee
to hold it down in there.
Hey. Who's the new girl?
Lolita.
What do you want now?
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Yeah. Crabs.
You gotta play
that thing so loud?
What'd you come out
like this for?
- Oral... hygiene.
- Oh, don't boss me.
- Liz?
- I wonder if they have
a back porch on that place.
Ooh.
Someday I'm gonna
give that she-cat
the whoppin'
she's been asking for.
[All]
Boo!
--Bring the law
down to her.
Let her know who wears
the pants around here.
Yeah, and who wears
the stupid-lookin' hat.
Be back in a minute.
That's a good one, eb.
I gotta give you that one.
--He's done back there,
i'll...
She'll be doing it.
Ha-ha, I soiled myself.
Go on, lem, and tell us about
that thing you killed
out there at the swamp.
Yeah, lem, let's hear
the rest of that.
Maybe we should have
subtitles for this.
I put five slugs
into that critter
before it went under.
Then I had
a few slugs myself.
And then I went under.
--Had regular arms on it,
like a man.
But made for a woman.
Sort of different lookin'.
Had suckers on 'em.
Tootsie pop, I think.
Like one of them...
Like one of them
octopus things.
No, that's octopi, actually.
Lem, you sure
that critter wasn't pink?
- Shut up, bruce.
- No.
I told you before,
it was sort of gray looking.
What, you gotta check
with string bean to laugh?
Well, laugh if you want.
- Hah.
- But that thing
weren't nothing
nature put out there.
No, sir.
And it weren't
no freak gator neither.
Maybe it was the rocket fuel
you've been drinking.
--This country for 40 years,
and I ain't never seen
nothing like it--
that's a double-negative.
--Too bad you didn't
bring it back.
Steve benton'd
probably pay a fair bounty
for whatever it was.
Bounty? I wouldn't
touch that critter
for all the money
ever made.
- Ten bucks?
- And if you'd seen it,
you wouldn't neither.
You'd better
take it easy on the stuff.
You're looking
kind of pinkered.
Oh, this is
an intervention.
Shucks, it's just
tobacco juice.
--Gonna clean my otter lines
out before morning.
Oh, no no,
not in front of us, please.
Lem, I think
that critter's a...
Ghost of one of those otters
you've been poaching
all these years
come back to haunt you.
Our joy grows, friend.
Well, if that's so,
you fellas'll
see it right quick
yourselves.
Yeah, that's great.
When you get near a sentence,
let us know.
Do you really think
this loitering
is good for business?
This sittin' around
plum wore me out.
The hooverville seven.
I think she knows
how to scratch an itch.
Ordinary pantyhose
are okay under funky clothes,
but gentlemen prefer hanes.
Huh, pete fountain.
[Men in other room laugh]
Quit wearing my things.
Boss hog, after dark.
Look. It's not like
I wanna be mean
or anything like that,
liz baby.
I got a reputation
around here.
As a big, fat,
insensitive guy?
These folks have no respect
for a man who lets
his woman boss him.
Well, next thing I know,
they'll be laughing at me.
Then I'd have to go
on a shooting spree.
--The rest of them--
won't you please
listen to me, liz baby?
[Joel hums]
- Liz?
- I'm not hearing you.
♪ La-la-la-la
la-la-la-la ♪
♪ hot child in the city ♪
My name's not liz.
It's blanche.
Hmm.
Oh, I love it
when she puts it on there.
I just like the smell.
Liz, honey, you think
you could lose some weight?
You know, she's gonna
shorten those calf muscles
- with those heels.
- Yep, you're right.
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
Stop looking at me
like that.
I'll look at you any way I want.
You're my wife.
Man, I do wonder
what it'd be like
to make love to you,
though.
No-- no,
don't do that, lady!
- Oh--
- it's okay.
Oh, mommy!
Honey west!
Joel, I thought underwear
was supposed to match.
It doesn't have to.
--Who do you think
you're talking to?
"Don't touch me?"
You're my wife.
I'll touch you
any time I feel like it.
He must have
a really good personality.
Can I call you sometime?
Where are you going?
A fella named humbert humbert
wants to see me.
Where are you going?
- I'm going out.
- To church.
Maybe I'll be back.
And maybe I won't.
- Liz, baby--
- do I have to guess?
Do I get a prize if-- i--
can I eat your dinner then?
Shouldn't've married her,
knowing that she loathed me.
Hey.
How come we're not moving?
[All grunt, strain]
Okay, all done.
Hey, it's jim from
wild kingdom.
Well, there was the young one
in that last trap.
- I had to kill it.
- Oh, poor thing.
Yeah, boo-hoo.
Told you
you shouldn't've come along.
So, let's have some kids.
But I love sitting in
the smelly pickup truck.
I can understand
hunting an animal,
but making it suffer
in those traps.
Hey, I suffer in
the trap of love.
Poachers know the swamp
like the backs of their hands.
But I'll catch one of them
in the act some night
and put him away
for six months.
- My, he's rugged.
- In the meantime,
I'll have to be satisfied
confiscating their trap lines.
- That's reward enough.
- There's enough traps,
it won't pay 'em
to keep trying.
Be careful, darling.
These people aren't
like other folks.
You know, they'll try
and get back at you.
And they've got
seven toes on each foot.
Steve,
you're a stranger here.
They've lived this way
for generations.
One man isn't going
to change them overnight.
Yeah, they gotta
want to change.
--A real worrywart.
- Well, I'm serious, steve.
They can be dangerous.
Okay. I'll be careful.
You just stop worrying.
Uh-huh.
Oh, he's the killer leech.
No, "lech." It's the attack
of the killer lech.
Oh, steve, I love you.
I love you so much.
♪ I don't know how to-- ♪
♪♪ [muffled]
- [Distant scream]
- What was that?
I don't know. You get in
that truck and lock it up.
Sounded like hee haw.
Could you leave
the mad dog here?
She dressed pretty formally
for a leech hunt.
Mm-hmm.
[Woman screams]
Oh, ricky, we were
just playing a little game.
Oh! Thanks for
comforting me with a gun.
Oh, he's a mess.
A chocolate mess.
Mm. Breakfast beans.
Oh, this guy's
the sheriff of everything.
--Ruled that sawyer died
in a misadventure.
Now, as far as
this office is concerned,
- that's the end of it.
- That's a common cause
of death.
Look, if lem was killed
by anything human,
I wouldn't need you
to tell me my job.
Ah, shut up
and finish your kaboom.
--Stompin' through the swamp,
looking for an overgrown gator.
What do I look like, a cop?
Sawyer wasn't killed
by an alligator.
Is that so?
Did you hear that, morton?
Game warden benton says
that wasn't a gator killed lem.
Well then, what was it?
You know so much,
go on, tell me.
- What killed him?
- It was low-level stress, troy.
--Defensive wounds
were the kind a squid
or a large octopus
might cause.
- I love squid!
- Oh, sure.
And did greyson explain
how a salt water creature
happened to be 30 miles inland
living in clear water?
Stranger things
have happened, I know--
look here, benton.
You work for the state.
- The state of confusion.
- Now, why don't you
keep your nose
out of county business?
Is that clear enough
for you?
Ah, go soak your fat head.
Okay then. Well,
I'll go get some soap and--
hey! Wait a minute.
What was that you said?
I said,
"go soak your fat head."
Is that exactly
how you phrased it?
Wasn't there more
of a lilting quality-- ah.
Boy, if I wasn't
so stuck with--
boy's looking
for bad trouble.
And he's sure gonna get it.
[Servo belches]
You can bet on that.
I thought
it was funny, sheriff.
Gary busey,
ladies and gentlemen.
Gary busey.
Look, I sneezed
on my dictionary.
So you see, the octopi
uses its suction discs
to hold its prey--
like I hold a sandwich.
--This will not
inflict a wound.
Same is true of the squid.
Now both creatures have
a parrot-like beak
as their primary offensive
and defensive weapon.
Well, maybe the sheriff
was right, dad.
I think I know
where the drapes went.
It could be a freak
or a malformed alligator.
Thanks for the coffee,
mrs.--
no. No,
I'm afraid it wasn't.
Well, where does that
leave us, doc?
- In the living room.
- Wish I knew.
You know, I'm beginning
to think lem was
telling the truth
in walter's store.
He did see something
that night.
Something that had
intelligence enough
to seek him out
and destroy him later.
- That was smart.
- Sawyer claims
to have killed
the thing he saw.
Put a half a dozen
rifle bullets into it.
I've seen
that old .44-40 he used.
Nothing could live after
being hit with those slugs.
Only half a cup?
Don't I like my coffee?
Conceding the possibility
of one such creature,
we must also concede
the possibility of others.
Oh, sorry, you lost me.
You know, this coffee's
wonderful.
--One sure way
of finding out.
Go in and search
every backwater channel
- and wet spot in the swamp.
- Any volunteers?
If it's there, I'll find it.
It all points
to one thing, drake.
This coffee's grand.
♪ From the land
of sky-blue waters ♪
[Joel and crow]
♪ water ♪
Ah, heck, honey.
I got a motor on this thing.
I just remembered.
Hmm, do you know
any other camp songs?
Uh, let's see.
"Barnacle bill?"
Yeah, whatever you do,
don't help me paddle,
ms. Dead weight.
Well, you know,
a visor might've been helpful.
Oh, it's a swamper.
Should we bring
our evil in here?
[Servo as hepburn]
Charlie, there's leeches
all over your back.
Sure is quiet around here.
What, is she on her lunch break
from wendy's?
♪ The wreck of
the edmund fitzgerald ♪
♪♪ [bots hum]
Here, leechy-leechy-
leechy-leechy.
Come on, nice leechy-leechy-
leechy-leechy-leechy.
Well, I'll tell you
one thing right now.
I am not going
to portage this thing.
You know,
maybe this isn't
the right time
to talk about this,
but I love muffins,
you know?
Those real fancy
nut and fruit muffins they got?
Full of whole grains--
kermit, no!
The heck?
- Did you hear something?
- Yes.
I heard you say,
"did you hear something."
Well, whatever it was,
it's not here anymore.
Eh, probably
over the state line by now.
Be quiet.
Phil harris and curt gowdy
are duck-hunting back there.
Did you want some coffee?
- Again with the coffee.
- Oh, thanks, hon.
Well, it is
very good coffee.
An army could hide in here
and never be noticed.
- No one did.
- What?
The seminoles
under osceola in the 1830's.
Ah gee, I was just
trying to break the ice.
I don't need
a history lesson.
--To round 'em up.
- I remember
reading about osceola
in high school.
Yeah, those seminoles.
Boy, they drink a lot of coffee.
Mm-hmm.
We've only been at it two days,
and I feel worn out.
Probably
'cause of my stories.
Might as well
keep on looking around.
Okay, well then.
Like some more coffee?
I'll get you some more coffee.
Dinner's ready back here.
Do you want rice-a-roni?
There's some steak tartar.
And some little
o'brien potatoes.
Hey, what's this
hole in the-- aah!
- I feel like
lewis and clark.
- Really?
You be jerry lewis.
I'll be petula clark.
[Servo mimics rimshot]
Well, I guess we may as well
give up for the day.
Well, you won't get
any arguments from me.
- Okay. Let's go.
- But I don't wanna go now.
What?
Will the leech survive?
Will they drink more coffee?
And will the fat guy's wife
ever touch him?
And what about naomi?
Hi there.
Look, either pick up a paddle
or sit still.
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
Is it asking too much
to pull over to a station
and ask for directions?
Men.
No. No.
Can we do something different
next time we go out?
Like go to a restaurant
or something?
Hello again.
I'm the leech.
See you later.
Well, let's see.
That'll hold me until
I get to the office,
anyway.
♪ Doin' the big fig newton ♪
♪ here's the tricky part,
the big fig newton ♪
I'm asking you for
the last time, dave walker.
Did you eat
the last moon pie?
Will you answer me,
you dirty old man?
Dirty old man? The ropers
get more action than us.
I ain't dirty, liz baby.
"Liz baby."
"Liz honey."
Can't you think of
anything else to say, stupid?
Gotta get this order
over to ms. Shoby.
She's one of my
better customers.
You know, I think
the bloom's off the rose.
Yep.
I love ya, liz baby.
But I love groceries more.
Get out.
Get out, you fat pig!
Now wait a minute.
I don't go calling you
a beautiful,
shapely woman, do I?
Oh. Cap. Okay.
Cleanup in aisle three,
please.
Listen, don't even ask.
All right?
--Trouble, do ya?
You know women, cal.
Gotta get the hair down
every now and then.
You sure do know
an awful lot about females.
Well, I was a female once.
I can't stand here
jawing, cal.
Gotta save my jaw
for eatin'.
--To ms. Shoby.
Here you go, ms. Shoby.
--This time.
- Well.
- [Servo, muffled]
- --Got himself killed,
she wants me to sell out
and move into town.
And leave all this?
Don't you let her
bamboozle you, dave.
Keep her right here
in the store.
After all, the place wouldn't
be the same without you around.
Well, there'd be more oxygen
for the rest of us.
Thanks, cal.
I'd better get going.
See you when I get back.
Yeah, I'll be around.
Oh, what a rich life, huh?
Flipping a walnut
in a sieve all day.
Heh heh, now I get my pick
of the wicker baskets.
♪♪ [Radio plays big band]
Hey, where are your
outboard motors?
- Oh, there they are.
- Liz baby?
Cora?
Uh, I'm here
about the affair.
I have an appointment
for two o'clock wednesday.
Say, could you
show me some sundries?
[Servo chuckles]
You want something, cal?
Do I still have
a tab going?
I sure do, honey.
Well, I'm real partial
to them hormel dinner meals.
What? What?
I'm not a mind-reader.
Wow.
Whoo. Boy,
some strong coffee.
I'm getting bugged.
My neckplate's quivering.
My cute little acrylic hands
are shaking and sweaty.
- Fill her up, joel.
- Yeah, that's it.
Anything you say,
little amigo.
Ooh. Sugar for me.
Okay, I'm right on it,
gypsy. No problem.
Boy, joel,
today's experiment's got bite.
It's like--
well, it's like
a fever dream, crow.
You know, or like
one of those dreams
when you get home
at midnight,
and you wolf down
a ukrainian sausage pastry
and a grolsch beer.
Then you go straight to bed?
Yeah, or when you just got off
a 12-hour shift at arby's,
and you're watching t.V.
At 3:00 am,
and then you fall asleep
during omega man.
- Yeah.
- Do you have any more
half and half?
Yeah, no problem.
You know, I had
a really weird dream
last night.
- I dream that--
- more.
We all got back to earth,
and then you guys got
a duplex together.
Well, you know,
just last night,
I dreamed that I had
a really nice girlfriend
with red hair
and a blue dress.
Then she turned into a gargoyle,
and I was really scared.
But then jesus came,
and everything was okay.
- You saw jesus?
- Well, yeah.
Real nice guy, too.
Thinner than you might think.
I don't remember my dreams
too often, joel.
Well, you know,
I never could either,
until I started
keeping a journal.
Hey, I'm curious.
What do you dream about, gypsy?
I dream I fly in color.
Oh, you dreamed you flew.
That means you're intuitive.
- That's really--
- I have one dream
about a little
french cafe in paris.
Right up
the rue de florentin.
What was that waiter's name?
[Bots]
Jean-luc!
Oh, you had that dream too?
We've got movie sign!
Careful, I spilled
a little coffee.
- Okay.
- I am wired.
[Crow growls]
I didn't hurt you now,
did I?
Why, it's just that
you're so strong.
Smelling, I mean.
I like a man who's strong.
You sure picked a doozy then,
marrying dave.
I don't think
he's got a muscle in him.
Just a big piece of flab.
You're talking about
the flab I love.
Oh, hon...
I didn't mean
anything against you.
I mean,
you're a little piece of flab.
Just that I can't see
a real woman like you
tied in with
a tub of lard like him.
I just can't imagine
you making love is all.
You wouldn't
understand, cal.
You know, i--
I've wanted to tell him.
I'M THE ROBIN McDONALD
FOR THIS REGION.
You just
wouldn't understand.
Hey, try me.
Free trial sample.
Try me for a week.
--All about it.
Sister, you got roots.
- Ooh.
- Huh?
Did you say something?
I wasn't listening.
- --To me.
- Clearly.
Kind of looks like a forest
up there in your nose.
If you told me
you killed your pa,
and your ma,
and your whole family.
I'll fight to protect you.
Mm-hmm.
Ouch. My keys.
Hey, remember my pa and my ma
and my whole family?
Well...
We now return
to fat guy goes nutzoid.
A troma presentation.
He's using
an adulteral decoy.
Come on, baby.
[Smooching sounds]
Ms. Shoby, I got
your groceries here.
Don't want
no trouble this time.
Like that guy could
sneak up on somebody, huh?
Honey, you making out with
one of my friends back here?
Hmm. Swamp blanket bingo.
Let's see now,
there's some trees
and a car and my wife
making out with-- oh?
First husband was
a no-good bum.
Second husband, no-good bum.
Third husband, no-good bum.
Use to get lashed up,
come home and beat up on me.
- Oh, merle haggard.
- Hey.
Or george jones.
He must've been
a prize pig.
One night he tried
to hold up a gas station.
But he wasn't very strong,
and it fell on him.
--Couldn't even run.
They caught him
less than a mile away.
Got set up.
I got a divorce.
Then I dated david soul
for a while,
and same thing.
After three years
living--
[bots snore]
[Servo snores, coughs]
Hey, she's really
opening up to him.
I wish it could've been me.
I'd know how to take care
of a woman like you, liz.
- [Servo growls]
- Maybe it's too late, cal.
Good thing they brought
a make-out tarp.
Mm-hmm.
I believe this is my dance.
You're wrong, woman.
It's too late
for the both of you.
She dropped a contact lens
in my mouth
and was trying to get it out
with her tongue.
Yeah, that's it, and--
now, get up.
Now look, dave, I know
what you're thinking, but--
I got double-large shot
in this here thing.
You got two seconds
before I pull the trigger.
O-kay. So I guess
I'll be seeing you
there, huh?
No point in
getting riled, dave.
Just advancing the flap.
Nothing personal.
She's been pestering me
for months to take her out.
Sure, cal. I understand.
Get her up so I can
get a better look
at the lying little tramp.
Oh, which one of us
is the lying l-- oh.
Come on, get up.
No! He'll kill me.
He'll kill me.
[Cal mutters]
When your husband wants
to take a look at you.
Uh, is this her?
You-- you walk
all the way, dave?
No, there's a motorcycle
in my pants-- what do you think?
- Get over there!
- Ooh.
Now-- now, david,
ain't as bad as you think.
- It's fantastic.
- Shut up!
- Tramp.
- What're you gonna do?
I'm gonna make you
listen to supertramp.
Dave, you put down
that gun before I get mad
- and make you eat it.
- Eat it? Mmm.
Hey, don't try
to distract me.
Go right ahead and try.
- [Gun blast]
- I know what you're thinking.
- Did I fire
one shot or only one?
- Move!
Every weekend,
I go through this.
Shh.
Oh. Just wanted the tarp.
♪♪ [All hum]
[Gunshot]
Now it's
the most dangerous game.
I'll say.
Oh...
This is more like
night of the iguana
than attack of
the giant leeches.
[Servo grunts, pants]
Quick, let's go
tell the camp counselor.
He'll help us!
- Come on!
- I can't go any further!
I got nowhere else to go!
[Crow pants, grunts]
You two go on without me.
Oh, wait a minute.
That's all wrong.
Thunder husband.
I'll catch you,
you wascally adultewers.
Wait a minute,
he's loading his gun
with tootsie rolls.
- Mmm.
- Mm. [Servo smacks lips]
Go on! Run!
Run till you drop!
Like I will!
Uh, let me guess.
She broke her heel.
Yeah, she's the girl.
She's supposed to.
Mm-hmm.
Now what is with the mud?
Did we miss some metaphor?
I don't know.
Sole of the soul,
or something?
[Servo chuckles]
Pull!
That one was
just for me. Hah!
I can't go on anymore!
Caleb, you've got to let me stop
- and rest for a minute--
- shut up! [Mutters]
- [Gunshot]
- Hey, that was his heart
blowing up.
I can't go on.
Caleb!
[Servo mimics branch snapping]
There's gotta be a trailer park
around here somewhere.
Man, look at all the weed.
Where are they,
tommy chong's backyard?
[Gunshot]
Suddenly,
they're the defiant ones.
Ahh.
[All]
Uh-- huh? Hmm? Oh--
welp, guess you
caught up to us.
Go on. Keep going.
Dave. Please,
you've gotta listen.
It wasn't my fault, honest.
She kept playing up to me
every time you turned your back.
- It wasn't my fault!
- I can't be held accountable!
And you call yourself a man!
She's got bosoms
and everything!
You and your muscles!
- Oh, she snagged on him.
- Shut up, you tramp!
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't be in this fix.
And my old friend dave wouldn't
be doing this thing to me.
- [Servo sobs]
- It's all your fault.
- Oh!
- She did it again.
Get going.
But-- but dave, dave,
we've been friends-- we've been
friends a long time, dave.
You wouldn't kill
an old friend, dave.
If you don't move,
I'll kill ya where you stand.
- But dave!
- [Servo sobs]
- [Gunshot]
- You brave, big man.
Hey, did he just kill him,
or what--
oh.
And as for you,
young lady, you're grounded.
- D'oh!
- They're melting.
- [Both scream]
- D'oh no!
- [Cal screams]
- Dave!
- Please, dave!
I'm sorry, dave!
Don't make us
go in the deep end!
We're not ready
for the deep end yet!
- No!
- [Liz screams manically]
Hey, quit laughing!
I'm trying to humiliate you.
--Honey, I'm sorry, dave!
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean it!
- I didn't mean it!
- Please, dave,
bring back
the chicken cordon bleu!
Please, don't leave me
to die, dave!
Oh!
You think
you'll learn enough
to stay away
from my woman, cal?
OH! I'LL LEARN PLENTY!
I'LL GET A PhD
in staying away
from your wife.
--I'll do anything
you say, dave. Anything!
- Would you rob a shop?
- ♪ anything ♪
Come on out of there.
Dave! David.
Give us a hand.
- Hmm?
- [Cal mutters]
- David.
- Aye carumba!
Oh my god.
Look out! Behind ya!
- David!
- I ain't fallin' for that.
Aah! Oh, dave!
[Servo mutters]
Uh, don't help
or anything, dave.
[Liz screams]
Gee, it was okay
to shoot 'em,
but this. Yuck.
Think they know we're here?
Ain't nothing
down here, sheriff.
'Cept for these
dead folks.
Well, I'm getting
tired of this.
Come on in, boys.
♪♪ [Servo hums]
Welp, if there was
any bodies out there,
we'd've found them.
I want some
straight answers, walter.
And don't give me
any more of that crud
about monsters, either.
Where'd you hide 'em
after you killed 'em?
[Servo belches]
Sorry.
To tell you
the truth, sheriff,
I didn't kill them.
I ate 'em.
Just wanted
to scare them good.
Oh, don't cry.
I hate it when you cry.
--Liz.
I wouldn't do
anything to hurt her.
I loved her.
I loved her more than
twice-baked potatoes.
You loved her.
That's why you chased her
through the swamp
with a shotgun.
Well, it's tough love,
admittedly.
Come on, walker.
Where'd you hide the bodies?
Won't you believe me?
It was some monsters, they--
take him out of here
before I lose my temper.
- Gary cooper in a cameo role.
- [Joel claps]
- Gary cooper,
ladies and gentlemen.
- [Crow whistles]
- Gary cooper.
- Yup.
Hey, it's bartles
and jaymes.
County pay a reward
if'n someone finds
a body, sheriff?
- Reward.
- $50.
And you get
to keep the body.
Those extra jeans
you need.
- Each?
- Yeah.
- Sounds like africa.
- [Crow squawks]
You know, I never
thought that of old dave.
Of course, everybody knows
that cal and liz had
a hankering for each other.
I think it went
way beyond hankering.
- Mm-hmm.
- Durn fools.
Grapplin' out there
in the middle of the water.
If'n them is still in there,
you can bet
some old bull gator's
got 'em stuffed
in his cave under the bank
- ew.
- Lettin' 'em ripen up
for a few days.
Jeb, you got
a real dark side.
Well, what we need now
is some long cyprus poles
to go in there
and pull 'em--
we'll drink
the palm dry, and--
no, no, no.
Otis, your quisp is ready.
- [Servo whistles]
- He's stuck to the ceiling.
Oh great, a swinger.
Always on my shift.
- Can we eat the quisp?
- For cryin' out loud.
I just love these hummels.
I'm sorry, doc.
I can't do it.
Well, I'd have
to do it myself.
Wouldn't wanna
have to arrest you, doc,
but I will if I find you
near the preserve
- with any explosives.
- Steve.
I'm sorry, nan,
that's the way it's gotta be.
- I'm a jerk.
- He's right, nan.
It's his job
to protect wildlife.
- What about human life?
- Hmm?
Three people have been killed
in that game preserve.
- Yeah? So?
- Doesn't that mean
anything to you?
Nan, try to understand.
- I'm a jerk.
- --Something in the swamp
was responsible
for those deaths,
I wouldn't hesitate
a minute.
We've been together
the last three days.
We didn't see
a trace of anything unusual.
Except for
that ten-foot leech.
Not so much as a suggestion
of any form of life
- unknown to us.
- Steve--
whoa. Easy-lift
needs adjusting.
All right,
I'll admit sawyer's death
left a lot of questions
unanswered.
But you can bet
your bottom dollar
the other died from
dave walker's shotgun.
Do you really believe that?
Figure it out, nan.
Walker admitted
chasing his wife and cal
into the swamps after
- he found them together.
- A cow?
Shot them, and he tried
to place the blame
on sawyer's d.T.'S.
- If sawyer told
of seeing...
- Hmm.
Purple giraffes
with polka-dot tails--
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Back up a bit, there.
There's one argument
against that, steve.
Dave walker wasn't
the kind of a man
- to hang himself--
- nah, he's a blade man
I talked with dave
less than an hour before
he killed himself.
- Maybe that's why.
- That man was in
a state of shock.
- I've seen--
- [joel yawns]
- Mmm. Hi.
- But I've never seen
anything to compare
with the horror
and the fear
in walker's eyes.
Well, he realized
what he'd done.
He killed two people.
One his wife.
- One his cow.
- Now look, doc.
Nan and I were
all over that swamp.
- And each other.
- Why didn't these monsters
attack us?
I've been thinking
about that.
They're probably
night creatures.
They can't stand the light.
They stay down near the bottom
- during the day.
- Oh, like comedians.
A small charge
would stun them.
Bring 'em to the surface.
Can't buy it, doc.
You're-- pig-headed,
steve benton.
No, it's steve-headed
pig benton.
Stubborn and pig-headed.
You just don't
understand, do you?
I'm a jerk.
Oh, I'll go
make some coffee.
She doesn't understand.
I'm a jerk, sir.
Yeah. Sure. Whatever.
- Good night, doc.
- Good night, jerk.
I'm a beaver, and this is
the view from my living room.
Enjoy.
♪ Home ♪
Hi, I'm back.
♪ O sole mio ♪
♪♪ [Servo hums]
Oh. Got any
deep-woods off there?
Well, at least we's paddlin'
in the same direction now.
Right over there
in them reeds--
is where my daddy
met my pappy.
I wish we could see him.
You can't personalize
a monster like this.
Ooh, hey, look,
a lot of golf balls
down in there.
Just can't figure
old dave out.
Welp, he's a complex fellow.
--Cal, what would you do?
I hadn't thought of that.
I hadn't thought of
anything, ever.
Right over there
in them reeds--
- yeah, jerry reed. Rex reed.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Willis reed. Donna reed.
- Lou reed. Reed richards.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Robert reed.
- Mmm.
These guys are
aggressively incompetent.
Don't look now.
I think they found jimmy hoffa!
[Servo groans]
Oh, take me
to the sweet
mushroom palace,
- my friend, booze.
- Boy, this is sure a hot one.
That's the suntan lotion!
[Crow coughs, gasps]
You ever feel like cryin',
and you don't know why?
- Sure is funny.
- Huh?
Gallagher.
Said he sure is funny.
- Noticed anything?
- Like what?
We've been proddin'
around here all morning.
- Huh?
- We ain't run across
a single gator.
And I don't have
no pants on.
By rights, this pool should be
crawling with 'em.
I'm crawling
with something.
- Sure funny.
- That is funny.
I don't like
the looks of this.
And I don't like
the looks of you!
- Let's call it a day.
- Well now, wait a minute.
We ain't poled the gator holes
around the bend yet.
Do what you wanna do, boy.
Just get me on dry land!
And right quick!
- Don't ever
get off the boat.
- All right, no use
getting all head up.
Let's go.
All right, now make that
motorboat noise again, caleb.
♪♪ [Servo mimics motor]
[Mutters]
By the way, can I borrow
your fondue set?
Sarah and her mother
are coming over later.
Oh.
Out here,
it's a wild goose chase.
Hey.
- [Screams]
- Ooh. Yeah.
This is the most fantastic
undersea odyssey ever filmed!
Uh-huh.
Oh, I just love
underwater love scenes.
Oh, great, the leeches
have a little fort.
Hello, bones.
Sorry about the formality.
This one's a keeper.
We eat tonight.
Hey steve,
you ever feel like
you're in
a gary larson cartoon?
Leeches are just
guys in fancy ponchos.
They're not leeches,
they're scientologists!
They're sears ponchos.
Oh look, jim henson's
cracker babies.
Huh?
[Screams]
Hey, keep it down.
We're trying to sleep over here.
We still haven't
got it right.
We don't want
hillbillies with good taste.
We want hillbillies
that taste good.
Hillbilly red.
Honey, wake up.
They're back.
Wow. He is gonna have
one immense hickey.
He's gonna have to wear
a turtleneck.
- Mm-hmm.
- [Liz screams]
How am I gonna
explain this to my husband?
Now this side.
Oh, puppies.
♪ You...
You've blown it all ♪
♪ sky-high ♪
You know,
if I didn't know better,
I'd say we're in
the dullest part of the movie
- right now.
- Probably.
♪ Without a reason why ♪
♪ there's a madman
across the water there ♪
Ooh, buzz bomb reference.
Hey, bab, you know,
I'm thinking about
gettin' me one of them
speedo swimsuits,
- what do you think?
- Look good, sweet pete.
Can we break for a snack?
Dave would've wanted us to.
We're under here.
You can't see us.
♪♪ [Mimics underwater voice]
Whoop, think my pants
are shrinking.
[Servo chuckles, coughs]
We're all clear!
Eh.
It's clear over here.
I'll be the judge of that.
- [Dog barks]
- Hey, that's not a scent!
That's the other dog
you're sniffin'!
These dogs have been
trackin' each other!
Liberty! Checkers! No.
Is it hot here,
or is it just me?
- Aah.
- [Frankenstein growl]
Whoa. Outta here.
Feets, don't feel me now.
Stay together, cheeks.
Well, this scene isn't
panning out like I'd hoped.
Hey, spread out.
This is my spot.
[Dog howls]
Yeah, yeah, we know.
You saw the best minds
of your generation
destroyed by madness.
- We know.
- All right,
let's keep moving.
To another film?
Champ! Rex! Spot! Otto!
[Servo mutters]
I claim this-a land
for the queen of spain.
♪ Wouldn't you
like to glide ♪
♪ in my beautiful balloon ♪
Yeah, they're really
having trouble with this scene.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's going nowhere.
- Well, we can't do
any more tonight.
- [Joel mutters]
Might as well start back.
Reckon ain't no use
hurrying now, mr. Benton.
- Oh, you reckon, do you?
- If reed and old sam was alive,
they'd've let us know
with a holler or something.
Yeah, it kind of
looks that way.
- Yep.
- You fellas
notice anything
about this lake?
- Uh, it's wet?
- I mean, the gators.
- What about 'em?
- They ain't here.
Piece of water this size
usually has maybe
50, 60 big ones around.
Whole lot of little ones.
Well, I could go for
a piece of water myself.
Well, maybe our torch'll
scare them away.
Nothing scares the gators.
Nothing.
Animal or human.
But keep in mind,
I'm intensely stupid.
Well, we might as well
get out of here.
T.g.i.f., huh, fellas?
Mm, hmong folk art.
We're worried about
your not-smoking, chad.
You got something
in mind, steve?
Yeah, remember
bub's daddy gum?
I'm thinking of what evan said
about the gators.
Yeah, he said, "aah!"
He said, "animal or human."
And yet,
something made them leave.
- Maybe a...
- Court order?
A mineral contamination.
I guess I'd better run
some water samples.
- Through myself.
- Come on, you two.
Drink your coffee.
Well, I was just talkin'
about coffee a moment ago.
And supposing
there is no contamination?
Well, we'll add some.
Then I'll send over
to eastport for a diving rig
and go down to look for
this monster of yours.
No, steve,
don't even joke like that.
You don't know
how to tell 'em.
I'm not joking, nan.
I had some training
with an aqualung
while I was in the navy.
♪♪ [Servo hums "aqualung"]
- ♪♪ [Joel drums knees]
- Two bodies we know for sure
are down there.
Maybe four.
They've got to be
brought up.
Wait a minute.
There are no alligators in
that part of the swamp, right?
- So?
- No sign of any
- fish or snakes?
- So?
No. What are you
getting at, doc?
Would you pass the jelly?
Well, there goes
your argument about
setting off
a dynamite charge
underwater.
- Hmm.
- It'd bring the bodies
to the surface.
- Hmm.
- Get it out of your mind, doc.
I'm not using
any explosives
as long as
there's another way.
- Why must you be such a--
- stud.
- Stubborn pig-head?
- Exactly.
- That too.
- I'll tell you why.
Number one,
there's bound to be
some aquarium life
in that section
even if the bigger forms
have abandoned it.
Get it?
An explosion underwater would
destroy every living thing
and wreck what nature
took years to build up.
Years of in-breeding,
destroyed.
Number two,
I'm paid to prevent
the useless slaughter
of wildlife.
Uh, what was one again?
Number three,
I'd have to get authorization.
To get that authorization,
I'd have to come up with
- a heck of a reason.
- Number four, you're a jerk.
Satisfied?
No, I could use more coffee.
Finish up, dad.
I wanna go home.
- I thought you were home.
- Steve...
How long would it take
to get this diving equipment
- from eastport?
- Is this a riddle?
A couple of days, why?
Oh, nothing.
Then why bring it up?
I was deliberately
wasting your time.
Take care of yourself,
steve.
Or someone might
stab you in your sleep.
Wait, I don't live here,
what the-- oh.
Well, here's hopin'.
Dad.
Can't you throw
the dynamite in from here?
No, I wanna get it out
into the middle.
In the deepest part.
'Cause pepperidge farm
remembers.
Now it's time for
trout-blasting in america
with your host,
dick brautigan.
♪ Oh-dee-doh,
I'm a danger ♪
♪ to myself and others ♪
♪♪ [all hum]
Well, goodbye forever.
I mean, dad.
Dad.
♪♪ [Servo hums]
Oh, I'm drained.
[Servo chuckles]
Mmm. That first sauna.
Big time.
Looks like
the cave of dr. Calamari.
Kind of fun.
I know, I know,
you get used to it.
♪ Love in an elevator ♪
♪ livin' it up
while I'm going down ♪
Eh, suck on that,
you darn son of a...
I pray I was adopted.
Well, honey, I threw it
under the boat,
where it would do
the most-- aah!
Parking at the swamp
sure is convenient.
- Yep.
- He's at it again.
Isn't he? Sad, really.
Well, let's go get him.
Gee.
Come on, dummy.
Back to the home with ya.
Look, now she's wearing
her beauty operator outfit.
It should go any minute.
Yeah, right.
What a loon.
I'm not a loon.
Next week, on macgyver.
Everybody into the pool!
[All guffaw]
Well, gee, it worked
on the gophers in my yard.
[All]
Huh?
[Servo makes bobbing sound]
What's that?
Hey, that's bob there!
- Oh.
- Get it? Bob!
Sorry.
Well, let me tell you,
if I could take
one dumb thing back
in my life.
I know what you mean.
Say, are those
bugle boy jeans?
- Hmm.
- Uh.
- I've seen better.
- Mm-hmm.
Just can't figure it out.
[All laugh]
Bring it down there, gypsy.
You know, fellas.
It's not easy
being a social misfit
and then getting
the added responsibility
of dragnettin' the swamp
for missin' townsfolk,
and I can't even
button my own shirt!
I hear ya, gunther.
Oh, isn't it amazing
how we inferior types
keep getting asked
to do dangerous work
that should go to men
more stable than us.
Really is a miracle.
Hooter?
Uh, duh, yup.
What next?
What did he say, silas?
Well, I think what
our bright young friend's
trying to say here is
the reason
we three goofuses
are asked to do
these hazardous tasks
outside the perimeter
of normal society's rationale
is we're a danger
to ourselves and others.
Oh, kinda reminds me
of darwin's theory
of natural selection.
Yeah, if you're dumb,
you die!
That's, I say,
that's a rich one there,
hooter.
[All]
Whoo.
♪ Oh, I'm a danger
to myself and others ♪
♪ my cousins are
as close as brothers ♪
♪ I stay out in the rain
all the time ♪
♪ he's a danger
to himself and others ♪
♪ only likes shows
with sally struthers ♪
♪ I can't even think
of a word that rhymes ♪
[Joel and servo]
But you did.
How dumb are you, uncle dad?
Well, pretty dumb,
that's for sure.
How dumb are you, uncle dad?
Well, this pipe's
filled with manure.
[All]
♪ we're a danger
to ourselves and others ♪
♪ screw the earth
and steal our mothers ♪
♪ leave us in the woods,
and we're just fine ♪
♪ we're a danger
to ourselves and others ♪
♪ good livestock
with better lovers ♪
♪ huntin' leeches,
what we call a good time ♪
[All]
Whoo!
Oh, boy.
I'd like to shake hands with
any giant leeches after that.
What, the dynamite,
or that crappy song?
- ♪♪ [Guitar outro]
- Woo-hoo!
♪♪ [All hum]
Good stuff.
Walker's wife.
Why didn't her body
come to the surface?
- Hmm.
- I don't know.
Maybe her shoes were
too heavy.
I think I'd better walk over
to the coroner's office.
What's the matter,
mr. Benton?
Feel awkward about arresting
my father in his own home?
- No.
- I warned him I'd arrest him
- if he used dynamite.
- Nice of you.
Jeez. I don't get women.
Well, the autopsy should
be over by now.
Oh, hi. You got the right
to remain silent--
I thought you'd be here.
I was wishing you weren't.
I don't want to have
to do this, doctor.
Do we have time for
a cup of coffee first?
- [Servo laughs]
- Sure.
Do you mind, honey?
No, I'll make
some sandwiches.
I'll make
some coffee sandwiches.
She's going to his place
to make sandwiches.
Ahh. You know,
liquor makes everything right.
- From the liquor council.
- It's what your body's
thirsty for.
--For all the good
it will do now.
Let me show you
my appendix scar.
--Help,
he didn't shoot cal.
Uh, I'll get more coffee.
I've just come from
the autopsies.
Kovis tried to keep me out.
I told him
I'd raise a stink
they'd smell
all the way to the capitol
- if he did.
- Oh, don't doubt that.
Well then,
what killed him, doc?
- Not drowning.
- No.
And cal wasn't shot, either.
And he wasn't
beat up by clowns.
Every drop of blood was
drained out of their bodies.
Turns out I did it.
Funny, huh?
And they had wounds
on their throats.
Suction wounds.
Like a...
Like a gigantic leech
might make.
Or a hoover.
And there's something
even more incredible.
- I'm skippy the chimp.
- --Was supposed
to have been killed
several days ago.
Sam and reed have been missing
a matter of 48 hours.
- Mm-hmm.
- All three of them,
as far as we know,
were in that lake
a minimum of two days.
Now, I'd stake
my reputation as a doctor--
- or what's left of it--
- that cal hadn't been dead
more than two or three hours
when we found him.
And the other two
less than that.
First stage rigor mortis
started in during the autopsy.
But how could that be, doc?
It's impossible.
The coroner will confirm it.
Cigarette?
Whatever killed them
is still in that lake,
and it's gonna take more than
dynamite to get it out.
[Crow as strangelove]
I think we should use
my new a-bomb!
Concussion from those charges
would've killed
a full-grown whale.
That's it! We'll put
a full-grown whale down there!
- Oh.
- That explains how
cal and the others lived
after they were
supposed to be drowned.
What do you mean?
Well, this whole region is
riddled by caves and caverns
cut out by the ocean
thousands of years ago.
- I love riddles.
- If there are caves
above the water,
then there must be caves
under the water.
- Go on.
- No. Make me.
Mike and I had
a chance to fool around
with some frogman equipment
captured from
the italian navy.
Yeah, then we went on
to showgirl costumes.
--Through a sunken transport
off salerno.
Butter cookie?
When the ship went down,
it trapped some air
- inside the hull.
- Mm-hmm.
We'd go down. Come up
inside the officer's lounge.
Take off
our face masks and...
Sort of sample some of
the bottles floating around.
Yeah, that's nice--
is there a point to your story?
--Driving us crazy
trying to figure out
how we were
getting the stuff.
You mean you think
that there's an outpocket
or a cave
underneath the lake?
Right. Gotta be.
How else could those people
have lived down there?
Not only that,
it explains how
whatever it is down there
lived through
the concussion.
- Steve.
- [As shatner] Steve!
Spock!
- Liz walker.
- I stood up too fast, whoo.
She might still
be down there.
Alive.
But musty.
Ew.
What?
- [Servo sighs]
- [Liz sighs]
Calgon, take me away.
- I think it did.
- Yeah.
This must be
the swimsuit edition
of leech illustrated.
No... no.
- No!
- Lick of paint,
some nice curtains,
this place would be okay.
Meanwhile,
on hollywood boulevard.
We now return to hawaii 5-0.
Looks like the cameraman
can't find the cast.
Oh.
♪♪ [All hum]
Skipper!
♪♪ [Servo hums]
[Crow as julia child]
Now you bring the swamp
to a rolling boil.
Hey, it looks like
the dad from flipper.
[Crow mimics dolphin]
Hey. Looks like
the whole town
came out
to watch him suit up.
Well, they don't have
a movie house.
Yeah, yup.
- Comfortable?
- Yeah.
Make a nice living.
You sure you don't want me
to go down before you, mike?
You haven't had
one of these things on
for a long time,
while me, every other day
I've been playing fish.
Remember the first time
we had one of these on?
Not this time, mike.
You ask me, they oughta
have their heads examined.
Giant leeches.
[All groan]
I'm willin'
to bet a month's pay
they don't come up with
nothin' more than excuses.
- Whoa, I could use ten bucks!
- It's crazy.
Him, the doc,
and his bride too.
Just wait'll I get on
the phone to the capitol.
I'll guarantee
somebody'll wish they kept
their nose out of
other people's business.
- And out of my
underwear drawer.
- I guarantee it.
[All groan]
Fool.
- Steve.
- I'm going with you.
Be careful, please?
Don't worry. Mike'll be ready
if anything goes wrong.
Don't worry about steve.
Now, if he were
going after a barracuda,
you might have
a tiny bit to worry about.
♪♪ [All hum
heart's "barracuda"]
Sure you don't
want some coffee?
Goodbye, gilligan.
Goodbye, skipper.
Sure hope those
coconut air tanks hold out.
♪♪ [All hum]
They're dead-- goodbye!
They don't have a chance--
so see you later, good luck!
We'll drag 'em out tomorrow--
good luck out there!
It's the star of
ralph bellamy, ralph bellamy,
ralph bellamy.
I see london, I see france,
I see little steve-o's
underpants.
[Liz sighs]
Good news.
We're having fish today.
[Crow chuckles]
Fish.
Eh, sorry.
No, no, please stay away.
No. You sucked
the life out of me.
I have nothing more to give.
Please.
Not exactly inviting, is it?
- Yeah.
- No, it sure isn't.
Hey, let's stay in the boat
and just eat sandwiches, okay?
And uh, look, I'll spit
in my own mask this time.
Right to the bottom.
Welp, let's try the other one.
Oh jeez, it's not deep.
It was filmed in
corman's swimming pool.
Eh. Darn fool kids.
Oh, watch that end.
Boonk! Oh, sorry.
It'll stop anything
up to a tiger shark.
But you gotta hit.
Misses don't count.
Now, anything goes wrong,
just yank on the line.
I'll be down in a hurry.
And yank real hard.
I might have the radio on.
[All groan]
♪ I'd like to be
under the sea ♪
...outside,
there's a little mailbox
that reads "I am a leech."
This must be his place. Ah.
What a jerk.
♪♪ [All hum]
Yank! Yank yank!
Hello! Is this thing on?
Oh! Big thing! Oh!
Huh?
Aah! Uppies! I want uppies!
[Servo sobs]
Eh, got a big one.
[Crow gasps]
Could you hand me
another spear?
You sure you don't
want me to go down
and finish it off
for you, steve?
No thanks, mike, i--
I think I hurt it
pretty bad.
Careful now. Anything hurt
is ten times as dangerous.
Yeah, I'll figure that out
underwater, friend.
[Servo chuckles]
He wounded it!
He's gonna finish it off!
I'd start the grill
if I were you!
Does he have
to go under again?
He's got to
make sure, honey.
This is what
therapy's all about.
Where could it have
come from?
I wish I knew.
We'll have to
make some tests.
- Like s.A.T.?
- Maybe the proximity
of cape canaveral's
got something to do with it.
The rocket station?
Well, they use
atomic energy--
- ♪♪ [joel hums]
- --In the first stages
of launches.
Not all of them
have been successful.
You think that
if some animal life
was close by,
not close enough to be killed
but close enough
to feel the effects
of a radioactive
energy that's--
a mutation.
A type of gigantism
- [servo snores]
- --Of some common animal.
Speaking of common animals,
how're you and steve getting on?
--I hope he's able
to bring it up.
[Servo chuckles]
Eh, I could bring my lunch up.
Let's go see what
steve the jerk is up to.
Hey, I can't see.
♪♪ [Servo hums with score]
Oh, feel like
I'm in hef's grotto.
[Sighs]
[Servo sighs]
Oh, there she goes.
Buh-bye now, buh-bye.
Oh, I've seen this
in dementia-13.
Oh. I see london,
I see france--
hey, come on. She's dead.
- Oh, sorry.
- Gah...
Hey. Good job.
They found her.
[Servo grunts]
I'll just put her
on the stringer.
- [Servo chuckles]
- That can't be liz.
Hmm.
I don't remember
liz being dead
with giant hickeys
on her cheeks.
What-- what could've
done that?
- Steven tyler?
- Look at her face.
Maybe.
The abyss.
Oh, owie, I just got
such a big blood blister.
And it's so nice and juicy.
And I feel so naughty.
And-- oh, I sure hope
a big leech doesn't come around.
Oh, that would be
just terrible.
Sucker!
Wait a minute, that's me.
[Crow laughs]
Ah, I dig me.
Now it looks like
a sea turtle.
Uh, think liz'll be okay
on the boat alone?
Hmm.
Steve was in trouble.
I had to act fast.
I had to get my sons
in the series.
[Servo as joe pesci]
Hey ma, I'd like to borrow
your butcher knife, okay?
Wait a minute,
are there two of them now?
- What's going on?
- Oh, it's a mess.
It's confusing.
Doesn't matter, huh?
W-- don't touch him!
That's my pal!
He's trying to stab
the cameraman.
Did you see that?
[Servo strains]
Not me, you idiot!
The leech! The leech!
Yeah, so there's
two of you, huh?
Come on, come on,
I've sucked blood
from guys bigger than
the both of you.
Then it was
back to the lodge
for a smooth canadian club.
Wha-- oh, it's a manatee.
[All groan]
I've been around here for years.
I never saw nothing
- like that before.
- I'm a professional skeptic.
Tommy bartlett invites you
to rid the wild leech.
Come on, let's all ride 'em!
Hoo-hoo!
David janssen.
Might wanna
measure and weigh her.
I think she's a keeper.
She's a record, all right.
Welp, there sure goes liz.
Well, have to go diving
more often.
- I'll carry her.
- No, I'll carry her.
- I'll get her.
And what of emily
and her love for chad?
And what of the hair
on chuck's chest?
Stay tuned.
Epilogue.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, who's this guy?
A roadie from sea hunt?
- Jeez.
- Wish I would've
thought of that.
♪♪ [All whistle]
- [Joel sighs]
- Okay, any time now!
- Gee, I hope that's right.
- --They must be
licking their wounds.
You sure you used enough stuff
to do the job, mike?
I used a hundred sticks
to 40%.
- Enough to kill all of us.
- Blow the bottom right out.
- All right, let 'er go.
- Oh no.
I've done enough
of your dirty work.
Help yourself.
[Servo chuckles]
No, I'm not falling
for that old one.
Hmm, now let's see.
How do you work this old thing?
Let's see if my memory
serves me correctly.
- Oh yeah.
- [Bots mimic plunger]
- Oh! Ooh.
- I blew my blanket clean off!
[All]
One.
Well, I'll be hog-tied
in a back room
with a big old--
- fish-fry tonight.
- [Servo chuckles]
[All]
Two.
I'd hoped that'd be
more exciting.
Well, let's go back
to town-- oh, wait.
There is no town.
Uh, who's hungry
for blood sausage?
Just kidding! Ha-hah!
Well, I'm gonna miss 'em.
Now we gotta go hang out
at the grocery store again.
[Servo sighs]
I feel empty.
Kind of a let-down, really.
But for the lowly detonator.
- Oh!
- Lost your head.
- My head! My head, grab it!
Gotta figure out
how this gonna end here.
There we go.
There we go, yeah.
Joel, I can't help
but feel that that film
was flawed in certain ways.
Well, what do you mean
by that?
Well, I don't know.
I guess I just felt that
corman failed to deliver
on concepts and ideas
promised us in films like
viking women
and the sea serpent.
You know, I had problems
with it too, joel.
Like, I can't figure out
if those leech creatures
were smart
or just big dumb monsters.
Well, they were smart enough
to take hostages.
Yeah, that's right.
And when that drunk poacher
fingered one of the leeches,
they sent a contract man
out to kill him.
Yeah, you know, so maybe
they kept everybody busy
at the swamp
while they went into town
and stole everybody's antiques.
- Oh.
- Well, I don't know
if they were that smart.
I mean, let's remember,
they did get caught.
I think they just went on
killing and killing
until it was
all about killing,
and it wasn't
about fun anymore.
Knowing what I know,
I guess that
they're smarter
than a sea turtle
but dumber than
danish physicist niels bohr.
Yeah, like,
I can see them going
to four of
the police academy movies
before they stop
shelling out the dough
and waiting for them
to come out on showtime.
Right.
They're the kind of leeches
that would probably
think of chili's
as their favorite
restaurant.
And it would never really dawn
on them that it was a chain.
Yeah. Or they'd be the type
to watch paid programming
and never figure out
that it was an ad.
Yeah. [Servo chuckles]
Well, this is
a lot of fun, you guys,
but I think it's time
to read a letter.
- Oh boy.
- Let's put this up on
still store, cambot.
Uh, this one comes from...
Jean-- jean a. Dunn,
and she writes,
"dear joel,
"I am positively crazy
about your show.
"When I can find it on tv,
"I tape it and play it over
so I don't miss
"any of your
sarcastic remarks.
"I keep recommending your show
to everyone I can.
"Everyone who is
lucky to catch it loves it.
"P.s. I am 59 years old,
and I've never written
a fan letter in my life."
Well, thank you,
jean a. Dunn.
Oh, bless you, jee-a-an.
- Jeanna dunn.
- Nice life goal.
Jean-nean-ean.
- Jean.
- What do you think, sirs?
[Leech slurps]
Oh, sorry, frank.
I left the leech on
too long.
Well, frank. Frank?
Well, now that
you've sucked all the blood
out of frank,
what're you gonna do now?
Oh, write, produce.
Be as creative as I can.
Have you thought about
the mad scientist game?
Hah! Don't get me started.
You know, I got some ideas.
Maybe we could do lunch.
- Sure.
- Oh--
you think you could pick it up?
I'm flat busted.
You know, I'd really
love to produce you.
I had this concept
that maybe we could go...